

Applicant for:

## Web Developer (.NET, C#, ASP.NET)

Starboard Asia Co.,ltd. 6 June 2019

### **An Tran**

- 1. What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?
- 2. When will you be able to join a company?

Note from ITviec: An Tran skipped the cover letter.



## Tran Thai An

Software Engineer

**Date of birth:** May 03, 1991

**Gender:** Male

**Phone:** +84 9 02 03 05 91

**Email:** tranthaian3591@gmail.com

**Address:** 04 Trinh Dinh Thao, Hoa Thanh Ward, Tan Phu

district, Ho Chi Minh City

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm An, a young guy, like to make friends, love sports, hard working and has the learning spirit. I joined DXC in Feb 2016 as an Associate Software Engineer in GLS RSS project (one of the oldest project in this company). My role consists of building and maintaining the eCTDXPress – DXC's electronic common technical document (eCTD) publishing the solution for the life sciences industry based on ICH and regional agency requirements.

Through each stage of this project, I gained for myselft a lot of experience from winform application skills to web application skills.

#### **SKILLS**

.NET Framework	3 years
C#	3 years
ASP.NET	3 years
MS SQL	2 years
JavaScript	6 months
HTML 5 , SASS, TypeScript, Angular 5/6	1 year
.NET core	1 year
Selenium	3 months
Language	English

#### **EDUCATION**

Sep 2014 - Apr 2018 University of Science Bachelors - IT

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

TOEIC Certificate with score 685 issued by IIG VietNam

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2019 - Present

#### **Multiple Language Tool**

Software Engineer

Main responsibilites:

1. Design UI and implement main function to translate current language of winform application to the target language (ex: China language, Japanese language...)

#### Website to Show/Add/Update Product Information

Software Engineer

Main resposibilites:

1. Design UI, database, code logic

#### Winform application to manage people information

Software Engineer

Main reposibilites:

1. Design UI, database, code logic

Mar 2018 - Present

#### TRS Publishing 5.0 (web)

Software Engineer

Main responsibilities:

- 1. Design UI and service for components.
- 2. Implement Clone function for eCTDXPress on Web.
- 3. Support implement validation functions
- 4. Working with VLM (an add-on support edit/create/delete... pdf files) on the web using PDFTron 5. Fix bugs.

Jun 2016 - Mar 2018

#### TRS Publishing 4.0 (winform)

Software Engineer Main responsibilities:

- 1. Read functionality requirement, user manual, technical design of the product.
- 2. Understand the framework for the product.
- 3. Implement and unit test following project requirements.
- 4. Implement and Decouple Clone function for eCTDXPress.
- 5. Support implement validation functions

Working with VLM (an add-on support edit/create/delete... pdf files)7. Fix bugs.

Feb 2016 - Jun 2016

#### GLS RSS 4.0 (winform)

Associate Software Engineer

Main responsibilities:

1. Implement and unit test Clone Function in eCTDXPress.

Implement and unit test Creat hyperLinks/bookmarks in VLM 3. Fix Bugs

Associate Software Engineer

Feb 2015 - Feb 2016 Main responsibilities:

1. Design and implement logic code for project.

### Xtablish project

#### **INTERESTS**

I like to play sports, especially football. Besides that, I also play badminton, play volleyball or go swimming when I have free time.

I often go coffee with my friends or see a movie or cooking at the weekend.

### **PROJECTS**

## **Wesite Product Information Project**

(2019 - Present)

Desciption	A Website that can show/add/update product information
Team size	1
My position	developer
My responsibilities	<ul><li>Analysis and design</li><li>Development</li><li>Bug Fixing</li></ul>
Technologies used	Net framework (web API 2.0) , C# - Entity Framework 6.0 (code first) - SQL - Angular 7 - Material UI - Typescript - HTML5 / SASS

## **Manage People Information Project (Winform Application)**

(2019 - Present)

Desciption	A tool that can manage people information
Team size	1
Team Size	
My position	developer
	- Analysis and design
My responsibilities	- Development
	- Bug Fixing
	Net framework 4.7.2
	- Entity Framework 6.0 (code first)
Technologies used	- SQL

## **Mutiple Language Project (Winform Application)**

(2019 - Present)

Desciption	A tool that can translate the current language of winform application to the
_	target language.
Team size	10
My position	Developer
	- Analysis and design
N	, ,
My responsibilities	- Development
	- Bug Fixing
	Net framework 4.7.2
	- OpenXLM
Technologies used	
Teemiologies asea	

## **GLS RSS project (Webform Application)**

(2018 - 2019)

Desciption	Migrate eCTDXPress winform application to web application
Team size	30
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analysis and design - Development - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	NET Core 2.1 , C# - My SQL - Angular 6 - Material UI - Typescript - HTML5 / SASS - Javascript

# GLS RSS project (Winform Application) (2016 - 2018)

<ul> <li>TRS Publishing suite consists of four applications: eCTDXPress, Publisher, VLM and ISM.</li> <li>1. eCTDXPress offers functionality for the building, reviewing, compiling, validating and archiving ofelectronic Common Technical Document (eCTD) submissions based on International Conference onHarmonisation (ICH) and regional requirements.</li> <li>2. Publisher offers functionality for the building, reviewing, publishing and validating paper CommonTechnical Documents (CTDs), non-eCTD electronic submissions (NeeSs), legacy/rest-of-worldsubmissions, clinical study reports and other generic reports.</li> <li>3. VLM (Virtual Link Manager) is an Adobe Acrobat plug-in for use as a standalone or integrated component of eCTDXPress and Publisher.</li> <li>4. ISM (Integrated Submission Management) is an administration and reporting console tool.</li> </ul>
30-50
Developer
- Analysis and design - Development - Bug Fixing
Net Framework 4.6.1, C# - MEF framework - My SQL

## Xtablish project (2015 - 2016)

Description	Build a project base on CRM framework.
Team size	10
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>- Analysis and design</li> <li>- Development</li> <li>- Review code</li> <li>- Optimize code</li> <li>- Bug Fixing</li> </ul>

Technologies used	- ASP.NET - Entity Framework - MVC
-------------------	------------------------------------